(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Sheldon:)I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper...
(Sheldon:)...and welcome to the premiere episode
of Sheldon Cooper Presents:
(Sheldon:)Fun with Flags.
(Sheldon:)Over the next 52 weeks...
(Sheldon:)...you and I are going to explore
the dynamic world of vexillology.
(Amy:)Hang on, Dr. C. What's vexillology?
(Sheldon:)Vexillology is the study of flags.
(Amy:)Cool.
(Amy:)I think I just learned something.
- Did you have fun doing it?
- I'll say.
(Sheldon:)Fun and information
are two sides to this video podcast.
Not unlike the only two-sided state flag:
Oregon.
(Sheldon:)Oh, look.
(Sheldon:)Hello, Mr. Beaver.
(Sheldon:)In future episodes,
we'll answer some burning questions.